A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Catalogued Reports, Reports 17727-19980 FA739G
Rockefeller Archive Center
- A case study in project analysis in transportation: improvement to the Hetauda-Narayanghat road (Nepal) (mimeo) III parts (Reports 018069) (DPM 71-39), 1971; Beyer, John C. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 71-39)
  Agricultural development projects -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Efficient reading and effective listening programme (mimeo) (Reports 018070) (DPM 71-40), 1971; Berg, Paul C. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 71-40)
- Employment and income generation programs (mimeo) (Reports 018071) (DPM 71-42), 1971; Tobias, George, 1912- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 71-42)
  Agricultural development projects -- India; Rural development -- India; Employment -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Urbanisation: aspects of urban income and employment (mimeo) (Reports 018072) (DPM 71-43), 1971; Rao, Arthur T. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 71-43)
- Note on the physical ecology of cities (mimeo) (Reports 018073) (DPM 71-44), 1971 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 71-44)
  Agricultural development projects -- India; Rural development -- India; City planning -- India; Employment -- India; Developing countries -- India
- A note on observed needs for research and planning in India toward employment and income generation (mimeo) (Reports 018074) (DPM 71-45), 1971; Tobias, George, 1912- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 71-45)
- Preliminary report on the characteristics of Suwana Block (Rajasthan) (mimeo) (Reports 018075) (DPM 71-49), 1971 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 71-49)
- Manual on quality control and testing of UCOPAN (mimeo) (Reports 018076) (DPM 71-50), 1971; Banerjee, K. K. (Kali Krishna), 1919-1983 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 71-50)
- Forestry and forest industries sectoral analysis (mimeo) (Reports 018077) (DPM 71-51), 1971; Gregory, G. Robinson, 1915- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 71-51)
  Prepared by staff members of the state planning project planning commission and Ford Foundation
- Data on the Indian economy 1951-1971 - research and analysis division, trade development authority, 16 Parliament Street, New Delhi (mimeo) (Reports 018078) (DPM 72-1), 1972 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-1)
  Economy -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Rural development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Pilot research project in growth centres - preliminary report on the characteristics of Basmath Block (Maharashtra) (mimeo) (Reports 018079) (DPM 72-2), 1972 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-2)
- Generalized system of preferences of EEC and Japan: a quantitative assessment of gains to India (mimeo) (Reports 018080) (DPM 72-3), 1972 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-3)
- Profitability analysis (mimeo) (Reports 018081) (DPM 72-4), 1972; Toksoz, Sadik (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-4)
- Calcutta, the leading edge (mimeo) (Reports 018082) (DPM 72-5), 1972; Row, Arthur T. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-5)
- Punjab and Krishna system planning studies (mimeo) (Reports 018083) (DPM 72-6), 1972; Toksoz, Sadik (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-6)
- An economic framework for project analysis in India (mimeo) (Reports 018084) (DPM 72-8), 1972; Beyer, John C. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-8)
  Some preliminary estimates - review draft.
- Evaluation: problems and possibilities for the training profession (mimeo) (Reports 018085) (DPM 72-9), 1972; Parkins, C. Richard (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-9)
  Economy -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Rural development -- India; Employees -- Training of -- India; Developing countries -- India
- The Ratnagiri fisheries project: a case study in social cost-benefit analysis (mimeo) (Reports 018086) (DPM 72-12), 1972; Mishra, S. N., 1942-; Beyer, John C. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-12)
- Notes for inclusion in the report of the special topic consultants to the Colombo plan consultative committee (mimeo) (Reports 018087) (DPM 72-13), 1972; Tobias, George, 1912- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-13)
- An economic framework for project analysis in India: some preliminary estimates (mimeo) (Reports 018088) (DPM 72-16), 1972; Beyer, John C. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-16)
- Personal comment (mimeo) (Reports 018089) (DPM 72-17), 1972; Parkins, C. Richard (Box 935, Sheet DPM 72-17)
- Planning for integrated area development: a procedure (mimeo) (Reports 018090) (DPM 73-2), 1973; Saini, N. S. (Nayan Singh), 1935- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 73-2)
  Presented at the 21st annual town and country planning seminar, Simla, December 27, 1972-January 2, 1973.
- Draft - policy on urban development - fifth five year plan, state planning board, government of West Bengal (mimeo) (Reports 018091) (DPM 73-7), 1973; Rao, Arthur T. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 73-7)
  Economy -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Memorandum on variety reduction in integrated area planning (mimeo) (Reports 018092) (DPM 73-9), 1973; Krishnayya, J. G. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 73-9)
- Formulation and economic evaluation of a bamboo afforestation project in Southeast Uttar Pradesh (mimeo) (Reports 018093) (DPM 73-11), 1973; Misra, D. N.; Susaeta, Eladio Saenz de San Pedro (Box 935, Sheet DPM 73-11)
  Economy -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Towards an operational approach to social cost benefit analysis (mimeo) (Reports 018094) (DPM 73-13), 1973; Herberger, Arnold C. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 73-13)
  Restricted from scholarly access.
- A health hazard index: a simple technique for identifying settlements which need extra health services (mimeo) (Reports 018095) (DPM 73-14), 1973; Mukherjee, Bishwa Nath (Box 935, Sheet DPM 73-14)
  Paper presented at the fourth seminar on planning methodology, pilot research project in growth centres.
  Economy -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Health planning -- India; Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Formulation and economic assessment of an intensive forestry project for the Bastar region of Madhya Pradesh (mimeo) (Reports 018096) (DPM 73-15), 1973; Tewari, N. D.; Susaeta, Eladio Saenz de San Pedro (Box 935, Sheet DPM 73-15)
- Micro-regional industrial planning (mimeo) (Reports 018097) (DPM 74-1), 1974; Thapar, S. D., 1928-; Banerji, Sures Chandra, 1917- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-1)
  Economy -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Regional planning -- India; Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Urban and rural planning thought Vol. XVII, No. 1 (mimeo) (Reports 018098) (DPM 74-2), 1974 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-2)
- District planning for service centres/growth centres - a technique (mimeo) (Reports 018099) (DPM 74-3), 1974; Saini, N. S. (Nayan Singh), 1935- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-3)
- Planning for education in a micro-region - an Indian case study (mimeo) (Reports 018100) (DPM 74-5), 1974; Dasgupta, Partha; Vinod Kumar, R. M.; Ramaswamy, Padmini (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-5)
  Education -- India; Economic development projects -- India; Regional planning -- India; Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- A note on industrialization policy and international technology transfer - some issues for policy research (mimeo) (Reports 018101) (DPM 74-8), 1974; Banerji, Shyamadas (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-8)
  Economic development projects -- India; Technology -- India; Regional planning -- India; Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Rural dynamics (mimeo) (Reports 018102) (DPM 74-15), 1974; Krishnayya, J. G.; Sharma, Suresh K., 1946- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-15)
  Draft - sectoral variables and intersectoral linkages in rural development.
  Economic development projects -- India; Regional planning -- India; Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Spatial efficiency of rural services in Junadadh district of Gujarat (mimeo) (Reports 018103) (DPM 74-16), 1974; Andrade, C. Preston, 1912-1978; Saini, N. S. (Nayan Singh), 1935- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-16)
- A simple method of obtaining a health hazard index and its application in micro-regional health planning (mimeo) (Reports 018104) (DPM 74-17), 1974; Mukherjee, Bishwa Nath (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-17)
  Health planning -- India; Regional planning -- India; Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Policy resolution analysis, inter-active evaluation (mimeo) (Reports 018105) (DPM 74-18), 1974; Sarly, Robert M.; Fisher, Howard Benjamin (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-18)
  Draft for discussion - approach to choices between complex policy alternatives.
- Urban and rural planning thought Vol. XVII, No. 4 (mimeo), October 1974 / (Reports 018106) (DPM 74-20) (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-20)
- A graphical approach to settlement planning for integrated area development (mimeo) (Reports 018107) (DPM 74-22), 1974; Andrade, C. Preston, 1912-1978; Banerji, Sures Chandra, 1917-; Fisher, Ruston; Saini, N. S. (Nayan Singh), 1935- (Box 935, Sheet DPM 74-22)
  Regional planning -- India; Rural development -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Rural growth centers: experiences in the pilot research project 1969-1974 (mimeo) (Reports 018108) (DPM 75-1), 1975; Fisher, Howard Benjamin; Rushton, Gerard (Box 935, Sheet DPM 75-1)
- Excerpts from third progress report central research cell, October 1975 of the pilot research project in growth centres of community development department, Ministry of food, agriculture, community development and cooperation, Government of India (mimeo) (Reports 018109) (DPM 75-3) (Box 935, Sheet DPM 75-3)
- A proposal for research into urban investment - decision making for Indian cities (mimeo) (Reports 018110) (DPM 75-4), 1975; Row, Arthur T. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 75-4)
  A draft for discussion.
  Economic development -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- A programme of research and training in multilevel planning for integrated rural development in India (mimeo) (Reports 018111) (DPM 75-6), 1975 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 75-6)
  A supplementary note on a multilevel planning project.
- Towards a program in public planning and management (mimeo) (Reports 018112) (DPM 76-2), 1976; Geithner, Peter F.; Row, Arthur T. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 76-2)
  Economic development -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Politics and government -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Energy strategies for India: an assessment of new energy technologies (mimeo) (Reports 018113) (DPM 76-3), 1976; Dalal, Vikram L. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 76-3)
  Economic development -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Technology -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Strategies for institutionalising public management education: the Indian experience (mimeo) (Reports 018114) (DPM 76-4), 1976; Chowdhry, Kamla, 1920-2006 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 76-4)
  Public administration -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Technology -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Manual for block level planning (mimeo) (Reports 018115) (DPM 76-5), 1976 (Box 935, Sheet DPM 76-5)
  Central research cell - pilot research project in growth centres.
- Goals for urban planning with reference to programme (mimeo) (Reports 018116) (DPM 77-5), 1976; Row, Arthur T. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 77-5)
  Reprinted from NAGARLOK Vol. VIII, No. 2, April-June 1976.
  Public administration -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- Umemployment perspectives (mimeo) (Reports 018117) (DPM 77-9), 1977; Sundar, Pushpa (Box 935, Sheet DPM 77-9)
  Labor supply -- India; Regional planning -- India; City planning -- India; Community development -- India; Developing countries -- India
- International economic relations: research and seminar networking possibilities in Northeast and Southeast Asia (mimeo) (Reports 018118) (DPM 78-3), 1978; Pande, Vijay G. (Box 935, Sheet DPM 78-3)
- An experimental investigation of changes in problem-analysis ability... (mimeo) (Reports 018119) (MI 65-18), 1965; Baumgartel, Howard, 1920- (Box 936, Sheet MI 65-18)
  India reports;Management, manpower & industry
  Industries -- India; Management -- India
- The Hindustan antibiotics, Ltd, Pimpri (mimeo), 1968 / (Reports 018120) (MI 68-5) (Box 936, Sheet MI 68-5)
- Notes on the nature of farm management (Reports 018121) (AG 59-3a), 1959; Malone, Carl C. (Carl Curtis), 1901- (Box 935, Sheet AG 59-3a)
  India reports;Agriculture
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Farm management -- India
- Some observations regarding associated research and evaluation of the IADP (Reports 018122) (AG 59-3b), 1961; Lionberger, Herbert F. (Herbert Frederick), 1912- (Box 935, Sheet AG 59-3b)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India
- Analysis and agricultural districts (Reports 018123) (AG 59-3c), 1961; Brown, Dorris D., 1911-; Malone, Carl C. (Carl Curtis), 1901- (Box 935, Sheet AG 59-3c)
- Plan for an integrated information programme to assist the IADP (Reports 018124) (AG 61-3), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet AG 61-3)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- Intensive agricultural districts programme quality (certified) seed programme suggested sanction note to each state (Reports 018125) (AG 61-4), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet AG 61-4)
- Comments on 'a model plan' for a district workshop center (Reports 018126) (AG 61-5), 1961 (Box 935, Sheet AG 61-5)
- The marketing of certified hybrid maize seed in India (Reports 018127) (AG 62-1), 1962; Brown, Dorris D., 1911- (Box 935, Sheet AG 62-1)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Seed technology -- India
- Proposal to assist cultivators with water use and management in the intensive agricultural districts programme (Reports 018128) (AG 62-2), 1962 (Box 935, Sheet AG 62-2)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Irrigation -- India
- The why and how of soil testing (Reports 018129) (AG 62-3), 1962 (Box 935, Sheet AG 62-3)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Soil management -- India
- The efficiency of various fertilizers for paddy (Reports 018130) (AG 62-5), 1962; Finfrock, Dwight C.; Donahue, Roy Luther, 1908- (Box 935, Sheet AG 62-5)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Fertilizers -- India
- Sambalpur paddy demonstration- 1962-63 (Reports 018131) (AG 63-3), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-3)
- Farm/village planning and redevelopment (Reports 018132) (AG 63-5), 1963; Eyheralde F., Rene (Eyheralde Frias) (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-5)
  A guide to define main areas for research and action.
- Reportfrom Raplph B. Greene to H.A. Miles and Douglas Ensminger (Reports 018133) (AG 63-5a, 1963; Greene, Ralph B. (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-5a)
- Opportunities for advancing agricultural mechanization in India and Southeast Asia (Reports 018134) (AG 63-8), 1963; Giles, G. W. (George Wallace), 1910-2003 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-8)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India
- Suggestions for a modern paddy handling, storage and milling facility for Thanjavur district (Reports 018135) (AG 63-10), 1963; Faulkner, Macon D.; Reed, G. W. (George William); Brown, Dorris D., 1911- (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-10)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Farm management -- India
- Estimated requirements for a model seed production, processing and storage unit for 100,000 acres of paddy - West Godavary District (Reports 018136) (AG 63-12), 1963; Finfrock, Dwight C.; Faulkner, Macon D. (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-12)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India; Farm management -- India
- Intensive agricultural district programme - report 1961-62 (Reports 018137) (AG 63-13), 1963; Microfiche, 4 sheets. (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-13)
  Expert committee on assessment and evaluation, Ministry of Food and Agriculture (Dept of Agriculture.)
- The art of agriculture in the Thanhauur district (Reports 018138) (AG 63-13a), 1963 (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-13a)
- Recommendation for establisment of a College of Agricultural Engineering at the Punjab Agricultural University, Ludhiana (Reports 018139) (AG 63-15), 1963; Stewart, Robert E. (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-15)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- Some preliminary thoughts on package program information work (Reports 018140) (AG 63-16), 1963; Webster, R. Lyle (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-16)
- Strengthening post-graduate studies in agricultural engineering at the Indian Institute of Technology, Kharagpur (Reports 018141) (AG 63-18), 1963; Hassler, F. J. (Box 935, Sheet AG 63-18)
- Sambalpur paddy demonstrations 1962-63 (Reports 018142) (AG 64-5), 1964; Herdt, Robert W., 1939- (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-5)
  Agricultural innovations -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- Intensive agricultural district programme (Reports 018143) (AG 64-8), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-8)
  Farm management report for 1962-63 147 farms records - West Godavari District.
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India
- The intensive agricultural district program (Reports 018144) (AG 64-9), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-9)
- Composite result demonstration guide (Reports 018145) (AG64-9a), 1964; Finfrock, Dwight C. (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-9a)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- Suggestions on revision and adoption of the first farm management extension manual in a particular country (Reports 018146) (AG 64-9b), 1964; Malone, Carl C. (Carl Curtis), 1901- (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-9b)
- A case study of two package program villages in Aligarh District (Reports 018147) (AG 64-11), 1964; Herdt, Robert W., 1939- (Box AG 64-11, Sheet AG 64-11)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- I.A.D.P. supply projections -fourth plan (Reports 018148) (AG 64-13), 1964; Brown, Dorris D., 1911- (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-13)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- Farm management study - effect of tenure on use of improved production practices on paddy Tanjavur District - IADP (Reports 018149) (AG 64-17), 1964 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-17)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Agricultural education -- India
- Role of soil testing in fertiliser use (Reports 018150) (AG 64-22), 1964; Leley, V. K. (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-22)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Soil management -- India; Fertilizers -- India
- The first step in advancing mechanization (Reports 018151) (AG 64-26), 1964; Giles, G. W. (George Wallace), 1910-2003 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-26)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India
- Soil acidity and the use of lime in India (Reports 018152) (AG 64-28), 1964; Bhaumik, H. D.; Donahue, Roy Luther, 1908- (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-28)
  Farm management -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India; Soil management -- India
- Using an 'information package' for intensive agriculture (Reports 018153) (AG 64-30), 1964; Webster, R. Lyle (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-30)
- Cooperative institutions and agricultural development (Reports 018154) (AG 64-35), 1964; Brown, Dorris D., 1911-; Miles, Harold A., 1906-1989 (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-35)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- Food enough for 540 million people - India in 1970 (Reports 018155) (AG 64-36), 1964; Kymal, P. K.; Brown, Dorris D., 1911- (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-36)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural education -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- Foodgrain procurement and distribution (Reports 018156) (AG 64-38), 1964; Brown, Dorris D., 1911- (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-38)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Rice -- India; Corn -- India; Wheat -- India
- Importance of materials and other resources (Reports 018157) (AG64-40), 1964; Brown, Dorris D., 1911- (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-40)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural engineering -- India
- Estimates of economic feasibility IADP rice mill evaluation project (Reports 018158) (AG 64-44), 1964; Brown, Dorris D., 1911- (Box 935, Sheet AG 64-44)
  Agriculture -- India; Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural processing industries -- India
- Impressions of the Ford Foundation IADP activity in India (Reports 018159) (AG 65-7), 1965; Anderson, Marvin A. (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-7)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India
- The district agriculture information officer: a new key post in India's agricultural development (Reports 018160) (AG 65-8), 1965; Webster, R. Lyle (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-8)
  Agriculture and state -- India
- A glimmer of light (Reports 018161) (AG 65-10a), 1965; Ensminger, Douglas, 1910-1989 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-10a)
- Justification for more power for agricultural production in India (Reports 018162) (AG 65-12), 1965; Rao, Swamy A. A. (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-12)
- An improved bullock harness for increased draft potentiality (Reports 018163) (AG 65-13), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-13)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Agricultural engineering -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India
- A survey of the Indian tractor ancillary industry (Reports 018164) (AG 65-16), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-16)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural machinery -- India; Agricultural engineering -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India
- The distribution of chemical fertilizers in India (mimeo) (Reports 018165) (AG 65-18), 1965; Brown, Dorris D., 1911- (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-18)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Fertilizers -- India; Agricultural innovations -- India
- Some responses of rice farmers to the package program in Tanjore District, India (Reports 018166) (AG 65-20), 1965; Malone, Carl C. (Carl Curtis), 1901- (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-20)
  Agriculture and state -- India; Agricultural development projects -- India; Rice -- India; Agricultural laborers -- India
- Rail head godown (Reports 018167) (AG 65-22), 1965; Giles, G. W. (George Wallace), 1910-2003; Parti, S. N. (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-22)
- Village level Godown (Reports 018168) (AG 65-23), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-23)
- Final report of my activities with IADP in India (Reports 018169) (AG 65-24b), 1965; Finfrock, Dwight C. (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-24b)
- Role of long term credit in intensive agricultural development (Reports 018170) (AG 65-28), 1965; Miles, Harold A., 1906-1989 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-28)
- First annual report of progress Ford Foundation -- Ohio State University Project (Reports 018171) (AG 65-31), 1965; Hill, Rey M. (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-31)
- IADP fact sheet (Reports 018172) (AG 65-38a), 1965 (Box 935, Sheet AG 65-38a)